YUSOOF MOHAMMAD

FLUTTER DEVELOPER OR/APPLIED AI ENGINEER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

KPAD, Pak Gatot II St, Bandung, 40158. Indonesia

PHONE

+628-12345-78-072

EMAIL

fuzuyx@gmail.com

PLACE OF BIRTH

Malang

LINKS

Website

LinkedIn

GitHub

<u>Twitter</u>

HOBBIES

I like cycling, a little swimming, and traveling a lot

I am a practical person and like doing things with my hands, and love turning caffeine into codes.

While if I had some free time, I used that to learns a new skill in AI fields and wanted to change my career path to become an Applied AI Engineer.

Some fun-fact about me: If I do stuck at both, I will travel to the mountains or beach without any electronics XD.

SKILLS

Git

Flutter

Dart

React.js

Node.js

TypeScript

Python

Firebase

PROFILE

Passionate and experienced **mobile developer** with several years of experience in **hybrid development, B2B software,** and **community-related** works.

Dedicated to building and fostering **positive** relationships with the **team, manager,** and **leader.** Even with **remote works** for more than a year.

Brings **beautiful** and **functional** application, a passion for aiding in the success of productions as a **knowledgeable** and **effective** developer.

Also, I have metrics that the application I build must have a solid **software architecture**, great **user experience**, **well code style**, and **documented**.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Flutter Developer, ARAH Akakia Teknologi

South Tangerang

Sep 2020 — Present

Builds Wellness Center:

- Healthcare solutions and all-rounder medical consult application.
- Slashed development time 40% by using Flutter, while ensuring the continuation and enhancements of services.

Mobile Developer, 360 Solusi Teknologi

Bandung

Nov 2018 — Present

- Develop and shipped interactive yet performant mobile applications <u>Mlaju</u> and AWAS.
- Built and shipped the <u>PMC Delivery</u> to help corporate tracking their parcel.
- Be in a team on **SCRUM** methodology resulting in self-discipline and increasing productivity.
- Identify and understand the personal values of superiors, subordinates, peers, and others.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Effectively overcome personal and organizational blocks to achieve results.

Professional Freelancer, B2B Software Solution

Jun 2018 — Present

Planned and implemented projects for corporate. Some that were relevant is:

- IKPI Build a mobile version of current web implementation with Web-view on Flutter.
- E Property Processes big data of property into a client-optimized Flutter application with a chart.
- One Medic Helps with bug fixing ongoing online reservation application for Wijayakusuma hospital.

And maintaining a **positive attitude** despite any hurdles.

INTERNSHIPS

Web Developer, Arca International

Jakarta

Nov 2016 — Oct 2017

- Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner.
- Worked well on a team-building company internal website projects like <u>ProgramBroiler</u>, <u>ArcaCorp</u>, etc_while learning the most of the programming basics here.
- Remained committed to a future vision and a solid idea of success.

Design Patterns

Data Engineering

B2B Software

User Experience

Object-Oriented Programming

System Architecture

JetBrains

Android

Windows

LANGUAGES

English

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

Indonesian

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet

EDUCATION

Business Administration, Nexford University

2021

Software Engineering, SMK Negeri 4 Malang

Malang

Washington

2015 - 2018

- · ESEMKAGRAF SRS, and web school forum discussion.
- More at soyfou[dot]xyz.

COURSES

The Complete Flutter and Dart Guide, Udemy

Sep 2020 — Present

Deep Learning Course with Flutter & Python, Udemy

Sep 2020 — Present

Data Visualization Basics, Dicoding

May 2020 — May 2023

SOLID Principle, Dicoding

Jun 2020 — Jun 2023

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Participant, OperationCode

Aug 2020 — Present

The largest community of **military** veterans, service members, and spouses committed to becoming software developers with the help of mentors, scholarships, and our tech partners. See *operationcode[dot]org[slash]challenge*.

OTHER THING WORTH MENTIONING

OpenSource Contributor

Mar 2020 — Present

Sustain local developer **community** while keeping open-source **awesome.** I made traces on:

- · Flutrans.
- · FlutterFire.
- · Neumorphic.
- · AMCC.

PROJECTS

Personal

Present

- <u>titanic</u> First Kaggle submission: Predict survival on the Titanic and get familiar with **ML basics**.
- mangoleh Personal website leveraging Gatsby.js and React.js with TypeScript. Showcase some of my projects and enhanced portfolio.
- <u>logeen</u> Demonstrate personal Flutter **starter** project with domain-driven design in mind.